吸血鬼日记 前情提要
Previously on "The Vampire Diaries"...
达蒙死了
Damon's gone.
我要你让我忘记我曾经爱上过他
I want you to compel me to forget that I ever loved him.
-达蒙 萨尔瓦多是谁  -他是个恶魔
- Who is Damon Salvatore? - He was a monster.
-我们到底在哪儿 -1994年
- Where the hell are we? - 1994.
我们永远也出不去了
We're never getting out.
有别人在这儿
There's someone else here.
如果要回家 我们要用魔法古物
To get home, we'll harness the power
控制好日蚀的能量
of the eclipse using a mystical relic.
这叫做运星
It's called an ascendant.
-你又在做那件事 -什么事
- You're doing that thing again. - What thing?
像个贱人一样的那个
Oh, the thing where you're a bitch
因为你喜欢某个人
because you like somebody.
这是我的女朋友艾薇
That's my girlfriend Ivy.
有人昨天晚上当着我的面杀了她
Somebody killed her last night right in front of me.
艾薇
Ivy.
你的朋友恩佐强迫我喝了他的血
Your friend Enzo made me drink his blood,
现在我只觉得非常渴
and now I'm just so thirsty.
吸血鬼杀了我妻子
Vampires murdered my wife.
我要找到他 以及他所有的吸血鬼同伴
I gonna get him to name all his vampire buddies.
- 你好 - 嗨 我是特里普 库克
- Hello? - Hi. Tripp Cook.
只是想谢谢你把吸血鬼恩佐交给我
Just wanted to thank you for turning over
他非常有用
that vampire Enzo to me. He's been very helpful.
恩佐么 我以为 嗯
Enzo? I thought, um...
我以为你会杀了他
I thought you were supposed to kill him.
哦 我会的 在我知道他做过的所有事之后
Oh, I will eventually once I know everything he does.
-所以他告诉你什么了 -听起来好像神秘瀑布镇的
- So what has he told you? - Sounds like the vampire problem
吸血鬼问题没有我想的那么严重
in Mystic Falls isn't as bad as I thought.
我是说 如果他知道一些名字 他会说出来的
I mean, if he had any names, he'd have given them up.
天知道我为了让他说话
Lord knows I've done plenty of things
做了多少事
to get him to talk.
嗯 听起来不错
Well, that's good to hear.
嗯 萨凡纳的事只是个意外
Yeah. Seems like it's moved on to Savannah.
我已经把我的一些人派到下面去了
I've sent some of my guys down there.
他们会检查它 看看他们发现了什么
They're gonna check it out, see what they find.
谢谢 嗯 谢谢你的提醒
Thanks for the, uh, heads-up.
创始人家族本来就是团结一心的 是吧
Founding families got to stick together, right?
必须的
Absolutely.
艾薇
Ivy?
你是在装修吗
You redecorated.
我大约应该告诉你 我杀了你的老板迪恩
I should probably tell you I killed your boss Dean.
他在林子里埋我的时候我醒来了
I woke up when he was burying me in the woods.
我喝干了他的血 但还是不够
I drank every drop of his blood, but it wasn't enough.
是的 我知道那感觉
Yeah. I know the feeling.
-那你为什么不帮我 -我正在试着
- Then why weren't you helping me? - I'm trying to help you.
就给我两袋血和上了关于日光的一课
Two blood bags and a lesson on sunlight?
哇 非常感谢
Wow! Thanks a million.
听着 我得把你带出萨凡纳
Listen. I have to get you out of Savannah.
嘿 因为你我死了
Hey. I am dead because of you,
因为你没有告诉我你是什么
because you lied to me about who you were,
因为你的朋友恩佐把我转变成了什么东西
because your friend Enzo turned me into something
就像吸血鬼猎人巴菲里面的角色
straight out of "Buffy the vampire slayer."
艾薇 淡定 当你变成吸血鬼之后
Ivy, calm down. When you're a vampire,
你的情绪会被放大
your emotions are heightened.
原来你也知道 看看我
You think?! Look at me!
我曾经是个有头有脸的人
I used to be a decent person.
我的成绩很好 回家过圣诞节
I got good grades, I when home for Christmas,
我有个很棒的工艺品店
I had a fricking etsy store!
-艾薇 拜托 -然后我现在成了杀人凶手
- Ivy, please. - And now I am a killer,
我要做的就是杀人 杀更多的人
and all I am gonna do is kill more and more,
这都是你的错
and it's all your fault.
吸血鬼
第六季  第五集
日记
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
合作贴吧：吸血鬼日记吧
-斯特凡 你怎么 -我需要你帮我个忙
- Stefan? Where have you... - I need a favor.
翻译：Krystle  小P  冬可可   校对：小P  Bunny
你在做什么 这个箱子又是怎么回事
What are you doing, and what is with this trunk?
等一下
Hang on.
哦 天哪
Oh, my God!
我在哪儿 你做了什么
Where I am I? What did you do?
时轴：络睿   压制：D  总监：络睿
-艾薇 这是怎么回事 -嗯 恩佐转化了他
- Ivy? How did this happen? - Uh, Enzo turned her.
然后斯特凡扭断了我的脖子 我醒过来就在箱子里了
Then Stefan broke my neck, and I woke up in a trunk.
对 所以我需要你忙个小忙
Right. So I need a little bit of help.
合作贴吧：吸血鬼日记吧
不
No.
不 不 不
No. No, no.
只是看着她一小会儿
Just watch her for a little while
我要去找卢克帮她做一个日光戒指
while I get Luke to make her a daylight ring.
给她看看绳子 教她控制自己 拜托了
Show her the ropes, teach her some control, please.
不 不 这个烂摊子和我没关系
No, no. This is not my mess.
这是你的烂摊子
This is your mess.
如果你不来找我
A mess that wouldn't have happened
它根本不会发生
if you had just left me alone.
嗯 我能听见你们说话 你们知道吧
Uh, I can hear you, you know?
我能听见很多东西 非常清晰的那种
I can hear everything, like, perfectly.
需要我提醒你这附近
Do I need to remind you that there is a vampire hunter
有吸血鬼猎人吗
lurking around?
他不在这儿 他在萨凡纳 这就是为什么我们不在那里
He's not here. He's in Savannah, which is why we're not.
你知道最悲剧的是什么吗
You know the real tragedy in all this?
我看到 他只是没那么喜欢你
I read "He's just not that into you," And...
闭嘴
Shut up!
听着 特里普库克不知怎么的
Look. Tripp Cook has somehow decided
变成了西边沿海地区自封的吸血鬼猎人
to become the eastern seaboard's self-proclaimed vampire hunter.
如果我们不能控制好自己 我们都有危险
None of us are safe if we can't control ourselves.
如果有人能教会她 那就是你了
If anybody can teach her, it's you.
是么 嗯 你不用恭维我
Yeah? Well, you don't have to flatter me
因为我已经知道了
because I already know that.
好吗 只要几个小时
All right? So just a couple of hours,
然后你就再也不用看到我了
and then you'll never have to deal with me again.
你以为这就是我想要的么
Is that what you think I want?
我不知道 你来说
I don't know. You tell me.
好吧
Ok.
我们什么时候吃东西
When do we eat?
返校活动
"Homecoming."
好吧 举手表决
All right. By a show of hands,
谁知道今晚返校活动的
who knows the supernatural origin
超自然起源
of tonight's homecoming party?
一个南北战争时期的战士 内森 惠特莫尔
A civil war soldier Nathan Whitmore
经历了枪林弹雨之后 脸部几乎毁容
horribly disfigured throughout countless battles
他努力在每场战争中活了下这样他才能回到家
somehow survived them all just so he could get home
回到他深爱着的女人身旁
to the woman he loved,
当他终于回到家的时候
and when he finally got home to his farm,
他发现她正在和他的兄弟上床
he found her in bed with his brother,
他做了每个正常人都会做的事
and did what any sane man would do...
他残忍地杀了他兄弟
He murdered his brother in cold blood
然后把他深爱的人
and then chased the love of his life
赶到了麦田里
out into the cornfields.
我等会得载一些器材到体育场去
I got to run some gear over to the football stadium later.
如果你愿意 我可以一会儿来接你
If you want, I could pick you up after,
-然后我们可以一起去 -你是说 像约会那样
- and we could go together. - You mean, like a date?
绝对不是约会
Because definitely not.
但是故事还在继续
But the legend goes...
那位惠特莫尔女士每年这天的晚上
That lady Whitmore is out on this night
都会穿着有她爱人血的白衣服
every year dressed in white, covered in her lover's blood,
跑过麦田 撕破喉咙地叫着一直到死
running through the cornfields, screaming for her life.
故事的寓意是什么 不要轻易爱上别人
And the moral of the story is? Do not fall in love,
尤其是你兄弟的女朋友
especially with your brother's girl.
好了孩子们 祝今晚你们玩的愉快
All right, kids. You have a fun night tonight.
注意安全
Be safe.
你知道么 那个警告的预言
You know, that cautionary tale
两周前对我说也许还能有点用
would have had more of an impact on me about two weeks ago.
达蒙也许已经死了 但我依然
Damon may be gone, but I can still find
能以评判他的人生找乐子
pleasure in judging his life choices.
说到这个 你现在有没有改变主意
Speaking of which, have you changed your mind
关于我强迫你忘记他的事
about me compelling you to forget about him yet?
你为什么要说 现在 说的好像失去了
Why do you say, "Yet," As if I'm gonna wake up one day
爱上一个连环杀手的不堪记忆
and realize that my life is over
会让我有天早上醒来
if I don't have the traumatic memories
-然后发现自己死了一样 -必须要问
- of loving a serial killer? - Had to ask.
你知道么 也许你是对的
You know, maybe you're right.
也许我犯了一个大错
Maybe I am making a huge mistake,
或者 也许我给了我自己一条非常珍贵的建议
or maybe I got a very valuable piece of advice
让我变得快乐
from myself about how to be happy
我正准备接受这个建议
and I intend on taking it.
今晚派对上我能看到你么
Am I gonna see you at the party tonight?
你知道么 我正在搅拌机上
You know, I'm waiting on the mixer
等待刚刚活过来的 渴望着什么的吸血鬼
for thirtysomething vampires just back from the dead.
-人太多了 -来吧 里克
- Less of a crowd. - Come on, Ric.
你离变成肖恩教授只差
You are like one hoodie and 3 missed haircuts
穿一件卫衣和三个月不剪头发了
away from becoming Professor Shane.
我呆在家就很舒服
I am perfectly content staying at home,
让我的头发长出来
letting my hair grow out.
你在逃避 你在变成
You're hiding. You're becoming
一个自我讨厌的吸血鬼隐居者
a self-loathing vampire hermit.
告诉你吧 你有了一个重新来过的机会
Tell you what. You've been given the chance to start over.
接受它吧 要快乐
Take it. Be happy.
我很快乐 有点吧
I am happy... ish.
正是 我8点见你 不过不要穿那件T恤
Exactly. I'll see you at 8:00 but not in that t-shirt.
这星期你穿了它两次
You've worn it twice this week.
你在这 很好
There you are. Good.
今天晚上你要出去么
Are you going out tonight?
在回校周末前的星期五么
On the friday of homecoming weekend?
不 我要学习
No. I'm studying.
真讽刺 多么意外的回答呀
Sarcasm. What an unexpected response.
我觉得你应该和我一起去玉米地迷宫
I think you should come to the corn maze with me.
玉米地迷宫
A corn maze?
嗯
Mm-hmm.
多萝西和托托会一起来么
Will Dorothy and Toto be joining us?
真可笑 你知道么
Hilarious. You know, there's an actual
事实上有一个专业词汇用来描述人们为什么要参加这种活动
scientific word for why people go to these invents.
-那是什么 -快乐
- And what's that? - Fun.
你想不想和我一起找乐子
Do you feel like having some with me?
得看情况了 你是不是准备
That depends. Are you gonna try
把我介绍给你的某些朋友
and set me up with any more of your friends?
看情况 你又准备用你的吻
That depends. Are you gonna kiss me
让我摆脱不快了吗
out of the blue again?
你这么说 我肯定不会
Not when you say it like that.
我得走了 还要邀请别人
I got to go. More people to invite.
你要邀请一群人做你晚上的约会对象
You're inviting multiple people to be your date tonight.
我邀请很多人一起找乐子
I'm inviting multiple people to join in on the fun.
至于我的约会对象是谁 由你决定
As for who my date will be, well, that depends on you.
这些年你第一次有好心情
You're in a good mood for the first time this decade.
因为我今晚要和我的女孩约会
Because I have a hot date with my girl tonight.
嗯 如果凯真的说了实话
Yeah, assuming Kai's telling the truth.
我在想共进晚餐和看电影
I'm thinking dinner and a movie.
你知道么 去他妈的晚餐和电影
You know what? Screw the dinner and a movie.
直接进入关键步骤
Skip straight to the good part.
对 假如我能完成那个咒语
Yeah. And assuming I can do the spell,
而我只有看到了才会知道它
which I won't know until I see it.
有希望么 邦妮
Whatever happened to hope, Bon?
记得我根本做不到的时候
Remember when I was all like, "Boo, grr,"
你总是说 太好了 太好了
and you were all "Hooray, hooray.
我们要离开这儿了
We're getting out of here!"
听着 我想回家胜过一切
Look. I want to go home more than anything,
但是凯是个疯子
but Kai's a sociopath.
谁能保证他不会搞砸一切
Who's to say he won't screw us over?
我 我这么说是因为我会杀了他
Me. I say because I will kill Kai
以及所有挡着我回家的人
and anyone who comes in the way of me going home.
我听到了我的名字
I heard my name.
我希望是好事
All good I hope.
日蚀正好在头顶上
The eclipse will happen directly overhead
正好和双子座排成一条直线
in perfect alignment with the Gemini constellation.
我们得在下面挖地道
You need to dig into the tunnels below us.
-我们会在那儿完成咒语 -为什么
- We'll do the spell there. - Why?
你们以前难道没有通过日蚀的力量进行过传送吗
Have you never portal jumped through an eclipse before?
好吧 听着 日蚀的光线会
Ok. Look. The light of the eclipse
照下来 然后运星就被激活了
will shine down and activate the ascendant.
你就说几句巫师用语 然后噗的一声
You spout a little witchy woo, and then poof!
我们围着亮光站成一圈
Anyone standing in the circle of light
把运星拿在手上 就能回家了
holding the ascendant goes home.
巫师用语 你说的是咒语吧
By witchy woo, I assume you mean the spell.
把运星给我看看
Let me see it.
现在还不是时候
When the time comes.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
回镇里 我得去拿一些很重要的东西
Into town. I need to gather some important supplies.
-你觉得怎么样 -我觉得你穿的是我的衣服
- Well, what do you think? - I think you're wearing my dress,
还有你肯定是聋了
and you must be deaf
因为我已经说过我们不会去那个派对的
because I already said the party's not happening.
所以你宁愿跟一个新生吸血鬼呆在这个屋子里咯
So you'd rather be locked in a dorm room with a newbie vampire?
不 我宁愿去参加派对
No. I would rather be at the party
就像我想拥有朋友一样
just like I'd rather have friends
尽管他这几个月一直无视我
who didn't ignore me for months
然后一有事需要帮忙就利用我
and then use me when they need help.
哇 终于知道了为什么斯特凡要带我来这
Whoa. Just realized why Stefan brought me here
跟你学学怎么自我控制了
to learn control.
对自己好点吧 解开束缚吧
Do yourself a favor. Unwind.
承认你对他有感觉不就行了
Just admit you have a thing for him.
你说什么
Excuse me?
我看到了你过来吃晚饭那晚
I saw the way you looked at him
你看他的眼神
that night you came over for dinner.
你还为他切东西吃
You practically cut his food for him.
你不懂 我们之间的关系
Oh! You know, my relationship with Stefan
真的是太 复杂了 好吗
is strictly... Complicated, ok?
你不是应该在练习熟悉
Aren't you supposed to be practicing
成为吸血鬼还是什么的吗
your vamping or something?
练好了 看到了吗 我很好啊
Done. See? I'm fine.
你已经把你的号码存在了我的手机里
You already put your number into my phone
让我有突发状况就联系你
as my emergency vampire contact.
我知道我一晒到阳光就会灼痛
I know I burn in the sun,
我们可以迫使别人 把他们抓来 吸完血 抹除记忆就了事
we covered compulsion and snatch, eat, erase.
天快黑了 快走吧 去参加派对
Look. It's getting dark. Let's go party.
你可以顺便教我怎么吸血又不会致死
You can teach me how to eat someone without killing them.
斯特凡就要到了
Stefan will be here very soon,
到时候在他的陪同下你想干什么都可以
and then you can do whatever you want with him.
那我们至少可以下下棋
Can we at least play a board game
或者做些和吸血鬼没关系的事吧
or do something non-vampire related.
终于出了一个好主意
Finally a good idea.
你想玩什么
What kind of game do you want to play?
我也不知道 拼字
I don't know. Scrabble.
我有锦标赛型 经典型
I have tournament, classic,
还有旅游适配型
and travel-sized.
啊
Whoo!
拉芙林医生怎么也在这
What's Dr. Laughlin doing here?
看起来好火辣
Looking hot.
我还以为她会永远穿着那件白大褂呢
I thought the lab coat was permanently attached.
是我邀请她来的
I invited her.
想为她牵线搭桥
It's kind of a setup,
只是他们双方都不知道而已
only neither party knows about it.
走吧 去展现你的迷人风采
Come on, time to get your Kansas on.
玉米地迷宫
斯特凡 我已经给你发了三条短信
Stefan, hey. This is the third message
通知你你的小蛇精病吸血鬼
alerting you that your psychotic little she-vamp
已经去嗨皮了
has gone AWOL,
还有你得知道 外面已经天黑了
and if you hadn't noticed, it's dark outside,
所以今晚如果有女生死了的话 所有帐都要算在你头上
so every dead sorority girl tonight is officially on you.
在另辟蹊径吗
Grading on the curve, huh?
喝酒根本没什么用
You know, this barely makes a dent.
不过也值得一试
Can't fault me for trying, though.
想要来一点吗
You want some?
不了 我只是过来跟卢克拿一个这个
No. I just came here to get one of these from Luke.
我来猜一猜
Let me guess.
你是在想 达蒙死了 这都是我的错
You played the "Damon is dead, and it's all your fault" Card.
你想干嘛 斯特凡
What do you want, Stefan?
恩佐和卡罗琳找到我后 他转化了一个吸血鬼
Enzo turned a vampire when he and Caroline found me.
你是说你那个萨凡纳的女朋友
You mean your girlfriend from Savannah.
那个你骗我 让我以为她是个巫师
The one you falsely led me to believe
可以帮达蒙和邦妮复活的女生
was a witch who knew how to help Damon and Bonnie?
她叫艾薇
Her name's Ivy.
我希望你能帮我催眠她去理解掌握好这一切
I was hoping you can compel her to get a handle on things,
还有让她离开我 去过她的新生活
get somewhere far away from me, live a good life.
你是在叫我帮你和她分手吗
Are you asking me to help you with a breakup?
我只是希望你能给她一个全新的生活
I'm just asking you to give her a fresh start.
是给你一个全新的生活吧
You mean give you a fresh start.
对不起 斯特凡 没有你想的那么简单
Sorry, Stefan. It's not that easy.
你催眠埃琳娜忘记达蒙的时候
Well, it was when you compelled Elena
也不是很难啊
to forget about Damon.
是你先忘了他的 兄弟
Well, you forgot about him first, pal.
他是我哥
He was my brother.
是啊 他也是我最好的朋友
Yeah, and he was my best friend.
在我催眠你变回我之前认识的
Why don't you get out of my face
斯特凡之前
before I compel you to be the guy
我劝你赶紧走
I used to know instead?
你吓到我了
You scared me.
真的吗 哪有那么可怕
Really? That wasn't scary,
不过这个就可怕了
but this is.
啊
Aah!
好了 我抓了一个人 吸了血
There. I snatched, I ate,
现在抹除记忆就行了
now erase.
什么抹除记忆
Erase what?
你到底在对我做了什么
What the hell are you doing to me?
我觉得我可能做错了
I-I don't think I did it right,
而且我也还没喝饱
and I'm still hungry.
老天 我一定会杀了你
Oh, my God. I am totally gonna kill you.
你快跑 跑 我说真的
You should go, run. Seriously.
我逊毙了
I suck at this.
嘿 你知道很有可能这个
Hey! You know there's a very probable chance
坟墓是你挖给自己的
you're digging your own grave
算了不说了
and not bothered.
哈
Huh.
看来我回来的正是时候
Looks like I got back just in time.
垃圾摇滚
Zima, grunge,
流行的亚历克斯新秀卡
every Alex Rodriguez rookie card in demand,
还有一个传呼机 你开什么玩笑
and a pager. Really?
号码555你好凯伊 我怎么舍得丢下这些好东西
555-Hiya-Kai. No way I'm giving those digits up.
这些就是你去拿的重要东西
These were the important supplies you had to get?
未来听起来很好玩 好吗
Look. The future sound great, all right?
我对互联网也超级期待
I'm superexcited about the Internet,
但是我大部分时间都是在1994年
but 1994 has been my home for most of my life.
所以带这些以解思乡之情
I'd hate to get homesick.
-所以我们现在下去吧 -不
- So let's get down there. - No.
在你告诉我咒语之前我们哪也不去
We are not going anywhere until you show me the spell.
好吧
Ok.
我们真的是哪也不去吗
Are we literally not going anywhere?
好吧 你不想告诉我咒语
Fine. You don't want to show me the spell,
那你就自己来
then you can do it yourself.
想要我的魔力
You want my magic.
你就拿走吧
Take it.
哇哦 她真的努力在装成很勇敢
Heh. Uh-oh. She's being brave.
我是认真的 凯伊 你最大的隐患不就是这个吗
I'm serious, Kai. This was your big threat,
不是吗
wasn't it?
如果我不念咒语 我们出不去
If I don't do the spell and let us out of here,
你就会拿走我的魔力自己施展
you'll just take my magic, leave me for dead,
不管我死活 现在就动手吧
and do the spell yourself. So go ahead.
全都拿走
Take all of it.
我真拿了你可别介意
Don't mind if I do.
邦妮
Bonnie?
没事的 我不会死的
It's ok. He won't kill me.
在我看来可不像是这样
Doesn't look like that from here.
啊
Ohh!
嘿 邦妮
Hey, Bonnie.
哇 你这家伙
Whoa, hey, guys.
住手
Stop!
他根本不知道咒语
He doesn't know the spell,
意味着 我们用不着他
which means we don't need him.
[咒语]
Motus.
不要 不要
No! No!
邦妮
Bonnie!
做得好 邦妮
Great work, Bonnie.
哦 我认出来了这个稻草人
Oh! I think I recognize this scarecrow.
每个稻草人你都是这么说的
You've said that about every scarecrow.
好吧 看来我们真的是迷路了
Ok. Well, then we are officially lost.
事实上 左转两次再右转三次就能出去
Actually, it's 2 lefts and 3 rights.
进来之前
I pulled up a satellite image
我截图了一个卫星图像
of this maze before I came.
哇 你是热衷于竞赛的类型 我懂了
Oh. Competitive type. Got it.
问题是 我是不是你喜欢的类型
Question is, am I your type?
说真的 真不是
Honestly, no,
但是人是会变的 是不是
but people can change, right?
哇哦
Uh-oh.
怎么了
What?
你还是对你的前男友念念不忘
You're still hung up on your ex.
野心勃勃的医科生
Overly ambitious premed student,
急于成为医生好证明给前男友看
desperate to become a doctor so she can prove
甩了她是犯了多大的错误
to the guy who dumped her that he messed up big time.
事实上 他死了
Actually, he died.
或者差不多那样子
Or that.
-对不起 我还以为斯特凡是 -他不是
- Sorry. I thought Stefan was... - No.
-好吧 -嗯
- Nice. - Yeah.
没事 没事
It's ok, it's ok.
他叫达蒙 但是今晚不属于他的事
His name was Damon, but tonight isn't about him.
今晚属于你和我
It's about you and me.
啊
Aah!
噢 一点都不好笑
Ohh! Not cool!
哈哈哈
Heh heh.
波旁酒教授 来得真是时候
Oh, Professor Bourbon. Perfect timing.
我还以为你早就在急救室见惯了
Imagine you see a lot worse in E.R.
我在那看到的都是自然存在的
Everything I see there is natural,
虽然恶心 但是不是人为化妆的
gross but natural.
僵尸 鬼魂 不死人 这些一点都不酷
Zombies, ghosts, the undead not cool.
是这样子啊
Good to know.
你有没有在这见到过埃琳娜
You haven't seen Elena around here, have you?
今晚可以说是她恐吓我来的
She basically blackmailed me into coming tonight.
哦 我来猜猜 她叫你走出教室
Oh. Let me guess. She told you to get out of the classroom,
享受一下生活
live a little?
哇
Aw.
她想撮合我们 好吧
We're being set up. Ok.
现在你就有点绅士风度 帮我离开这里
Now why don't you be a gentleman and get me the hell out of here
因为我们实在是太老了
because we are way too old for this party,
而且我想去喝一杯
and I need a drink stat.
-我还以为你是个洁癖鬼 -这次就破一下例
- I thought you were a germaphobe. - I'll make an exception.
这派对好烂
给你5分钟过来找我
我告诉你会很好玩的 是不是
See? I told you it would be fun.
天啊
Oh, God.
不要
Oh, no.
救命啊
Help.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey.
埃琳娜
Elena!
埃琳娜 过来这边
Elena, get over there.
哦 天哪
Oh, God. Oh, my God.
情况多严重
H-how bad is it?
好的 我来吧
Ok. I got this.
你也做不了什么
I'm not sure there's anything you can do.
我会尽我所能的
I'll do everything that I can.
去看看别人需不需要帮忙 好吗
Just go see if you can help someone else, all right?
走吧
Come on. Go.
听我说
Listen to me.
你躲得很是时候
You dove out of the way just in time.
你真是命硬 现在赶紧走
You were very lucky. Now get out of here
能带走多少人带走多少
and take as many people as you can, ok?
走
Come on.
泰勒
Tyler?
-我刚才开着车 埃琳娜 -什么
- I was driving the truck, Elena. - What?
这个家伙迎面向我冲过来
This guy ran right in front of me,
现在他受伤很严重
and he's hurt bad.
如果他死了
If he dies,
我又会变成狼人了 知道吗
I'm a werewolf all over again, ok?
我需要你过来帮我 我们在一条沟里
I need you to get here. We're in a ditch.
我也不知道这是哪里 但是你得过来帮我
I don't know where, but I need you here now,
求你了 快过来
so please hurry.
泰勒 你不知道
Tyler, you don't understand.
你的车冲过了迷宫
You drove right through the maze.
现在这里到处都是受伤的人
There are injured people everywhere.
那我应该怎么做
What the hell am I supposed to do?
听着 别挂
Just... listen. Just hang on.
你得让他醒着
Um, make sure that you keep him awake.
看看他伤得多重 我去找乔和阿拉里克
Assess his injuries while I go find Jo and Alaric.
你在流血
You're bleeding.
我没事
I'm fine.
你有事 我看看
No, you're not. Let me see.
等等 怎么回事
Wait. What the hell?
那应该不是我的血
I don't think it's my blood.
好吧 干起活来又得多费些手脚
Oh. Ok. That's gonna make things more difficult.
我得带你出去
I really think I should get you out of here.
不 我不能走
No. That's not an option.
你脸色怎么这么苍白 你晕血吗
You look pale. Does blood make you squeamish?
是 有一点
Yeah. Something like that.
不用担心 你会习惯的
Don't worry. You'll get used to it.
-报警 跟紧我 -好
- Call 911, follow me. - Ok.
谢天谢地
Thank God!
你把她弄丢了
You lost her?
所以你是几百万小时过后
Oh, so you decide to listen to your messages
才看短信的吗
a million hours later?
不 我没有弄丢她 是她扭了我的脖子
No. I didn't lose her. She snapped my neck.
-你怎么这么久 -我有事做
- What the hell took you so long? - I got caught up.
你有什么事做
You got caught up, doing what?
-当时我已经开车走了 -你要走
- Driving halfway out of town. - You were leaving?
我把日光戒指放在了你的门前
I slid Ivy's daylight ring under your front door.
我不在乎什么狗屁戒指 斯特凡
No! I don't care about some stupid ring, Stefan.
你真的想把你的吸血鬼前女友
Were you seriously about to dump
丢在我这
your vampire ex-girlfriend onto my lap
然后你就脱身离开
and then just skip town?
天哪 你现在到底变成了什么人
God, who are you right now?
我变成了努力想过新生活的人
I'm someone who's trying to start over,
但是你和恩佐突然出现
and then suddenly, you and Enzo show up,
害到我现在被人追着跑
and now I have hunters on my trail
还有个新生吸血鬼想要杀了我
and a brand-new vampire who wants to kill me
还有她沿途遇到的所有人
and everyone else in her path,
这还让我怎么重新开始 卡罗琳
and that's not how someone starts over, Caroline.
你知道最糟糕的事情是什么吗
You know what the worst part about all of this is?
一个月以前 我希望达蒙能够回来
Is about a month ago, I wished that Damon would come back
因为我知道这样的话
because I knew if that happened
你也会回来的
that I'd get you back, too,
但是现在 我唯一希望的
but right now, all I want is for you
就是你赶紧回到车上然后滚蛋
to just get back in your car and go.
你在哪
Where are you?
我做了一件坏事
I did a really bad thing.
噢 你是指折断我的脖子吗 这我已经知道了
Oh, you mean, break my neck? Yeah. I noticed.
好吧 那就是两件 听着 我很抱歉
Ok. Two bad things. Look. I'm sorry.
告诉我你的确切位置然后在原地等我
Tell me exactly where you are and stay put,
我这就来找你
and I'll come get you.
嗯 嗯 嗯 嗯
Mmm. Mmm, mmm, mmm.
你能不能消停一会儿让我好好集中注意力
Can you stop and let me concentrate?
往好处想 这表示这东西不赖
On the bright side, this stuff's not so bad.
还是水果味儿汽水
It's fruity and fizzy.
达蒙 我还有事要忙
Damon, I'm working on something.
往坏处想 这表示你智商堪忧
On the not so bright side is your intelligence
因为你毁了我们唯一能够离开这的机会
because you took the only chance
还把他变成了一个
of us getting out of here and turned him
巨大的
into a giant...
尸串
Douchekabob.
你想一下 达蒙
Think about it, Damon.
什么样的监狱会给囚犯钥匙呢
What prison gives an inmate a key?
这是个脑筋急转弯
Is that a trick question,
还是这东西真的开始奏效了
or is this stuff actually starting to kick in?
我觉得双子座女巫聚会
I think the Gemini coven
用贝内特的咒语创造了这个地方
used a Bennett spell to create this place.
万一这就是为什么外婆把我送到这来的原因呢
What if that's why my grams sent me here?
一般我听不懂你在说什么的时候我都会摆出这副表情
This is the face I make when I don't understand you.
你知道吗 我外婆对我说过的最后一句话就是要保持强大
You know, the last thing my grams said to me was to stay strong.
她会不会就是在告诉我
What if that was her way of telling me
我有能力出去
I have the power to get out?
我有运星
I have the ascendant,
可以看到许多天文现象
a massive celestial event to draw from,
再加上想早日摆脱掉你的欲望
plus a burning desire to get away from you.
怪不得凯不会杀掉我
That's why Kai wouldn't kill me.
他需要贝内特女巫
He needed a Bennett.
只有我才能让他离开这里
I was his only way out of here.
喂 你要去哪
Whoa. Where are you going?
回家
Home.
来吗
You coming?
-怎么了 -我把这孩子给撞了
- What happened? - I hit this kid in the road.
不是我的错 只是一场意外
It wasn't my fault. It was an accident.
恩 不过也是件好事 对吧
Yeah, but that's a good thing, right?
-你知道我什么意思 -无所谓了
- You know what I mean. - It doesn't matter.
如果他死掉的话 我
If he dies, I'm...
打给埃琳娜
Call Elena.
救护车已经在路上了
Ambulances are on the way.
好的 过来 我需要你帮助
Good. Get over here. I need your hands.
好的
Ok.
把手放在这 这样能止住血
Put your fingers right here. That should stop the bleeding.
这样我好检查他其它部位
While I can look at the rest of him.
-你还好吧 -恩 我很好
- Are you doing ok? - Yeah, I'm fine. Wow.
用手压住股动脉就行了
Just keep your finger on that femoral artery.
好的
Ok.
他的脉冲正在下降
His pulse is still dropping.
你不是第一次遇到这种情况吧
This isn't your first rodeo?
听着 我上完医学院之后参加过军队
Listen, I was in the army right out of med school.
家庭原因 那时只想着逃避
Family stuff. Just had to get away.
拉芙琳医生 我的朋友泰勒 他遇到麻烦了
Dr. Laughlin, my friend Tyler, he's in trouble,
听起来很糟糕 而且我不知道他在哪
and its sounds really bad, and I don't know where he is.
叫我乔就行 把扬声器打开
Call me Jo. Put him on speaker.
好
Ok.
-泰勒 听得见吗 -我不知道该怎么做
- Tyler, can you hear me? - I don't know what to do.
他应该是失去意识了
I think he's losing consciousness.
我要你准确地回答我的问题
Need you to answer my questions as accurately as you can.
-出血了吗 -很多
- Is there blood? - Tons.
现在还在流血吗
Is it still flowing? Is he bleeding now?
不 看起来没有在流血了
No. I... it looks like it stopped.
他的鼻子或嘴巴里有没有出血
Is there any coming out of his nose or his mouth?
有
Yes.
什么颜色 红的还是黑的
What color is it? Is it red, or is it black?
黑色的 黑的很吓人
It's black. It's really freaking black.
-我们要怎么做 -握着他的手
- What do we do? - Take his hand.
然后呢
Now what?
试着让他感觉好点就行
Just try and keep him comfortable.
撑不了多久了
Won't be long now.
是时候了 达蒙
It's time, Damon.
很好 又要尴尬了
All right. Let's get awkward.
这样吗
Like this?
恩
Yep.
我敢肯定要是有的选 你选择任何人
I'm sure there are about a billion people
也不会选我和你一起在这里
you're rather be here with.
不一定
Not exactly.
走吧 啊
Let's go... ohh!
啊
Unh!
你们是不是忘了谁
Forgetting someone?
你们真的以为
Did you really think I hadn't tried
我以前没有试过自杀吗
to kill myself before?
我试过 很多次
Because I had, lots of times,
各种方式
lots of ways.
你要是拿那个 下只箭就瞄准她的心脏了
Grab that, and the next arrow goes in her heart.
选择吧
Your choice.
我在这 没事了
I got you.
不 噢
No! Ohh!
达蒙 不要
Damon! No!
加油 老兄 求你了 一定要活下去
Come on, man. Please, you've got to live.
加油啊 兄弟
Come on, buddy.
坚持住 你不能死
Come on, man. You can't die!
够了 泰勒 停手
Stop! Tyler, stop!
停手吧 好吗
Just stop, ok?
已经没有办法了
There's nothing you can do.
我杀了他
I killed him.
不 你没有
No, you didn't.
是我杀了他 丽芙
Yes, I did, Liv.
我们已经做了能做的一切
Everything we've tried to do to keep me from this,
没想到这家伙突然会跑到路中间来
and all it took was one guy running out into the road.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
丽芙 不要 住手
Liv, stop, stop!
你这是在做什么
What the hell are you doing?
你没有杀他 泰勒
You didn't kill him, Tyler.
是我杀的
I did.
嘿 救护车来了
Hey. The ambulances have arrived.
乔说让医护人员把她抬走
Jo said to let the paramedics take it from here.
我觉得她可能等不了了
I don't think she can wait.
她的气管已经
Her windpipe, it's...
学术上讲叫偏移
Deviated is the medical term.
其实就是扭曲了
Screwed is more like it.
不管怎样 她现在很缺氧
Either way, she's not getting enough air.
利亚姆 我能帮忙
Liam, I can help.
很好 把她的头按住然后我来疏通她的气管
Good. Stabilize her head while I trache her.
你之前做过吗
Have you ever done this before?
用西柚实验过 不算成功
Practiced on a grapefruit. Didn't end well.
不 利亚姆 我不是这个意思
No, Liam. That's not what I meant.
其实我可以
I can actually...
成功了
It worked.
-你真的做到了 -不用这么惊讶
- You actually did it. - You don't sound so surprised.
邦妮 离开这儿
Bonnie, get out of here.
我出不去了
I'm not gonna make it.
啊
Unh!
但你可以
But you are. Motus.
不要
Don't!
不
No.
No!
啊
Aah!
噢
Ohh.
感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
你真的想知道吗
You really want to know?
我刚吃了几片止疼药
Because I'm hopped up on pain meds
想告诉你各种恶心
and just obnoxious enough to tell you.
我会慢慢听的
I'll take my chances.
我觉得你很伟大
I think you're great.
勇敢 幽默风趣
You're brave, funny,
大概是我见过的
not to mention maybe the most attractive man
最有吸引力的男人了
I've ever seen,
我毫不避讳的告诉你这些
and I feel completely comfortable telling you this
因为我已经成熟并且知道自己想要什么
because I'm old enough to know what I want.
你可能认为我疯了 不过我觉得我是注定了要认识你
And call me crazy, but I think I was meant to know you.
现在该你说点什么了
This is the part where you say something
或者亲一下 或转头就走
or kiss me or run for the hills.
没错
Yeah.
我觉得你很聪明伶俐
I think you're amazing, brilliant,
是我见过的最性感的女人之一
and one of the sexiest women I have ever met,
并且我相信 你和我
and I would love to believe that you and I
原本是天造地设的一对
were meant to be
因为我知道除了我现在所过的生活之外
because I would love to believe there was a plan for me
我还有一个别的计划
other than this life that I am living right now.
但是今晚很不愉快
But tonight was a disaster.
你觉得我很无聊 还是个酗酒者
You thought I was boring and a borderline alcoholic,
因为你还不了解我 还不了解真正的我
and because you don't know me, not the real me anyway,
所以你不打算亲我
you don't want to kiss me,
你非常希望我能够转头就走
and you absolutely want me to run for the hills.
你说的对
You're right.
今晚真的很不愉快
Tonight was a literal disaster,
你完完全全就是个酗酒者
and you're definitely an alcoholic...
但你一点也不无聊 里克
But you're far from boring, Ric.
你在哪 我已经站在这好久了
Where are you? I have been standing here
感觉像过了一个世纪
for a hundred years.
别大惊小怪的 我快到了
Don't exaggerate. I'm almost there.
要帮忙吗
Need any help?
我听说学校里发生了一场不小的意外
I heard about the, uh, big campus accident on my scanner.
有人受伤了还是怎么
I heard someone got hurt or something.
我很好
I'm fine.
不会吧 你在流血呢
Actually, you're bleeding.
不可能受到惊吓了
You might be in shock.
赶紧走吧
Please just go.
我不能
I don't think...
这样就行了
There we go.
很好
Ok.
那个穿得像惠特莫尔小姐的女的
So that girl dressed like lady Whitmore,
我都准备放弃她了
I was ready to give up on her,
但你能够救她 为什么
and you were able to save her. How?
我也不知道 新手运气比较好吧
I don't know. Beginner's luck?
埃琳娜 她应该已经死了的
Elena, she should have died.
但她没死
And she didn't.
这个世界上有很多疯狂神秘的事情
There are crazy, mysterious things in the world,
就连科学也无法解释
I mean, some things science can't explain.
举个例子
Name one.
好吧
Ok. Um...
为什么婴儿要做第一次呼吸
Why does a baby take its first breath?
一种反应能力 一个新的肺里的液体
A reflex. The fluid in a newborn's lungs are...
我原本以为亲我比死亡更可怕
I thought kissing me was a fate worse then death.
你之前问我喜欢什么样的类型
You asked me what my type is.
今晚你就是个英雄 完全令人瞠目结舌
You were a hero tonight, an absolutely jaw-dropping
绝无仅有的英雄
and out-of-this-world hero.
我就喜欢这样的
That's my type.
我们关门了
We're closed.
我和埃琳娜谈过
I talked to Elena.
关门了
Still closed.
她说其他人都活了下来
She said everyone else lived.
你不想和我谈谈都发生了什么吗
You don't want to talk about what happened?
没有什么好说的
I've got nothing to say.
今晚你杀了人
You killed someone tonight.
你不可能假装什么都没发生
You can't just pretend that didn't happen.
- 看看我 - 丽芙
- Watch me. - Liv.
丽芙
Liv.
他死了
He was dead.
你没有办法救活他
There was nothing you could have done to save him,
所以你决定拯救我
so you saved me instead.
是你救了我
You saved me.
无论我做什么也报答不了你这份情义
I can never repay you for that.
我所能做的就是答应你 决不浪费你的心意
All I can do is promise you that I won't waste it.
哈
Ahh.
是的
Yep.
这都是真的
This is happening.
我要对着这个放着我家人尸体
I'm gonna talk out loud to a...
的地窖自言自语了
A crypt filled with my dead family.
除了你 达蒙
Everyone but you, Damon.
因为不管你在哪
Because wherever you are,
你都不会在这
it's not here.
我必须得说
I got to say...
没有你我过得并不那么好
I'm not doing so great without you.
我一直试着重新开始
I keep trying to start over,
但是
but...
我无法做到
I can't get anywhere...
因为我还是很茫然 哥哥
Because I'm lost, brother.
我很困惑
I'm lost.
那又怎样 离开了几个月而已
So what? Gone a couple of months,
你就可以这样浪费
you think it's ok to waste a perfectly good
这么上好的波旁威士忌吗
bottle of Bourbon?
啊
Ahh.
-达蒙 -是我
- Damon? - Yep.
活生生的人
In the flesh.
-我现在怎么可能看到你 -因为我还没死 斯特凡
- How can I see you right now? - Because I'm not dead, Stefan.
我说 这酒是挺好 但比不上
I mean, this stuff's good, but it's not
我看到了死人 那种感觉
"I see dead people" Good.
哼
Heh.
说来话长 弟弟
It's a hell of a long story, brother,
总而言之我回来了
but I'm back.
我回来了
I'm back.
没错
Yeah.
我回来了
I'm back.